

Shalom David

MUSIC TEACHER

Contact

Address

NEW DELHI, INDIA 110049

Phone

9654989082

E-mail

shalomdavid007007@gmail. com

Skills

Music teacher

Very Good

Music lessons

Good

Musical arrangements

Very Good

Musical composition

Very Good

Music Theory

Good

Languages

Hindi and English.

Very Good

Summary Certified music teacher offering over 5years'& 5months of experience closely working with students in western music, distinguished by professionalism and perfect communication skills, demonstrated in pleasant personality and effective listening **Proficiency Offered**. Proficient with music instrument Piano and Keyboard.

Music Teaching: Guided individuals and groups in playing Piano & Keyboard

Teaching Objective - To train individuals and groups with best of musical knowledge, and guide them to become proficient artist with art of music

To seek and maintain full-time position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, excellent time management and problem-solving skills.

Additional Information

• D.o.B 07-05-1990

 Marital status: Single Nationality: Indian Religion: Christianity

Languages known: Hindi and English

Work History

2015-05

Convent Of Rani Jhansi School R.K Puram Sec

- Coordinated recitals and musical events to showcase student achievements.
- Communicated with parents regarding upcoming events and student progress.
- Conducted group music lessons lasting from 30 to 45 minutes each.

2016-08 -2017-05

Western Music Teacher

Shalom Hills International School, Gurugram Guided individuals and groups in playing music instruments

Provided music lessons on the instrument: Piano

- Collaborated with team members to achieve target results.
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment.
- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships.

2017-07 - Western Music Teacher

2017-08 St. Martin's Diocesan School, New Delhi

• Developed and maintained courteous and

2019-04 -2019-11

Western Music Teacher

effective working relationships.

Tagore International School Vasant Vihar , New Delhi

.

- Participated in continuous improvement by generating suggestions, engaging in problemsolving activities to support teamwork.
- Learned new skills and applied to daily tasks to improve efficiency and productivity.

Private Piano Teacher

Delhi School of Music, New Delhi

- Conducted individual music lessons lasting from 30 to 60 minutes each.
- Established strong music foundation with students by incorporating basic music theory into weekly lessons.
- Arranged lessons to accommodate each student's unique goals and interests.
- Developed musical instruction with goal of end-of-term recital performance.
- Preparing Individuals for Music Exams by Trinity & Abrsm

2019-02 -Current

Private Piano Teacher

Mezzopiano School of Music, Gurugram

- Conducted individual music lessons lasting from 30 to 60 minutes each.
- Established strong music foundation with students by incorporating basic music theory into weekly lessons.
- Arranged lessons to accommodate each student's unique goals and interests.
- Developed musical instruction with goal of end-of-term recital performance.
- Preparing Individuals for Music Exams by Trinity & Abrsm

Education

2011-02 -2011-11

Bachelors of Music: Piano Grade 2

Trinity College of London U.K

2011-12 -	Bachelors of Music: Piano Grade 4
2012-12	Trinity College of London U.K 4 Piano (Merit
2012-09 -	Bachelors of Music: Piano Grade 5
2013-12	Trinity College of London U.K - K 5 Piano (Passed
2015-12 -	Bachelors of Music: Piano Grade 6 Theory
2016-06	Trinity College London, U.K
2017-12 -	Bachelors of Music: Paino Grade 7
2018-10	Trinity College of London U.KK Grade 7 Piano (Merit
2016-10 -	Diploma : Computer Applications
2017-12	Swami Vivekanand Subharti - Meerut
2015-12 -	Bachelor of Arts: Sociology & English
2018-12	Swami Vivekanand Subharti University - Meerut

Accomplishments

Participated in group/solo and duets singing competitions.

- * Performed solo's and group instrumental in competitions
- * Served as Sports Captain in 10+2.
- * Played for YMCA organization and with different bands across in Delhi and performed with Classical chorale with Delhi School of Music & Theme Music Institute's Choir and Orchestra.

Interests

Travelling with Friends & Family

Music

Food

Live Sound Engineering